That's pretty obvious!
Looking good, Vanisher.
They're headed into the tunnel.
I'm that kid's only hope,
so sit tight and
wait for my word.
Whatever.
We're gonna lose 'em.
I'm dropping in.
Uh, that's a negative,
sole survivor.
Luck is not a superpower!
We are so fucked!
No, we most certainly
are not fucked.
Seriously, I don't get it!
What, you shoot luck
lasers out of your eyes?
It's just it's hard to picture.
And certainly not
very cinematic.
I mean, luck?
What coked out,
glass pipe-sucking
freakshow comic book artist...
came up with that
little chestnut?
Probably a guy who
can't draw feet!
Once again, it all
falls on my shoulders.
It's why I'm cursed
to be a solo act.
Wander the Earth... I'm in.
I'm sorry, what did you say?
I'm in.
How in the fuck are
you in already?
Oh, shit.
It's Cable. 12 o'clock.
Okay.
New plan. Use all of
your imaginary powers
to stop Cable from
killing that kid.
I'm coming up on your six.
That gun is amazing!
Hey! Asshole!
Where is he? I can't see him.
He's on top of you.
He's tearing you open!
He's going in through the back!
Oh, God, he's inside!
You hear yourself, right?
Accidental double entendres!
Russell! Russell Collins!
Hands off that kid, John Connor!
No, no, no!
Shit!
Two can play that game!
Got it! No, I don't.
Showtime, mama!
Lady Luck, take the wheel.
I'd ask who you are, but
you'll be dead in a second.
I'm Domino, and doubtful.
Hang in there, Doms!
Oh, this is really hard.
And give me back my
Skee-Ball token.
You're doing great.X-Force.
I guess dubstep never dies.
Whoo!
You killed Black Tom, you
racist son of a bitch!
That's unfortunate.
We got no brakes!
Figure it out!
There's nothing I can't kill.
Well, as Scoutmaster
Kevin used to say...
"There's a first time
for everything, son."
Give me your best
shot, One-Eyed Willy.
Those bullets were,
like, super fast.
Here we go.
Domino, mind slowing us down?
Here goes nothing.
Knock, knock.
That's my boy.
Holy...
I'll be first to admit...
this did not go
according to plan.
I'll also be the
first to admit that
that plan was written in crayon.
Looks like Russell found
a new friend. Jelly.
Turns out Domino's
a bit of a badass,
and maybe, possibly
mildly lucky.
But Cable? Ugh. That
guy's in a mood.
A mood that is
about to get
significantly worse.
Something is so terribly,
terribly wrong.
Oh.
Oh, God, that hurt.
Suck it, Mel Gibson.
Russell.
Russell!
Russ, where are ya?
Russell. Russell, you're okay!
Oh, thank God. Oh, my God!
Juggernaut!
I thought that was you!
I should've worn my white pants.
You probably get this a
lot, but I am a huge fan.
Uncanny X-Men183. Thor411.
X-Men Unlimited12.
You know, it has always
been a dream of mine...
to see my face reflected
in your helmet...
as you charge at me
with murderous intent.
I don't mean right now.
I'm gonna rip you in half now.
That is such a
Juggernaut thing to say.
Oh, my God! I can't
feel my legs.
I can't feel...
Oh, no, they're right here.
Got 'em. God, Russell.
I have a mission.
To get my revenge.
I'm going to burn that
headmaster alive.
You're not the revenge type.
Take it from a friend.
Friend? You were sick,
and I protected you.
You said it yourself.
"I'm not your friend.
Find someone stronger."
So I did.
Russell, I couldn't
protect you back then.
But I can now. What do
you want me to say, huh?
"I care about you"?
'Cause goddamn it,
I care about you, Russell.
What's Juggernaut got
that I don't have?
Don't you say legs! I know
you're gonna say legs!
Legs! Still hurts
to hear out loud!
What is that? That's
not a real rope!
You get back here, young man!
Doms!
Doms, get me out
of here, please.
Use my arms as backpack straps.
I think we may have found
your cosmic reason
for being here.
I'm pretty sure this isn't it.
X-Force.
No child is hopeless.
Don't give up on the boy. How
could he just walk away?
It was the coldness in his eyes.
You should've heard it.
I guess family
really is an F-word.
Rub my legs, Mama.
Why would I rub your legs?
Please, they hurt. I
have growing pains.
What in the...
Why is your hand so tiny again?
That's not my hand.
Oh! Mary, mother of Joseph!
That was nice for me.
Wade! I heard what happened
with the convoy and...
Why wouldn't you cover that up?
A warrior has nothing
to be ashamed of.
Yeah, but you do. Look at you.
You're just straight
shirt-cocking it,
toddler-style.
Oh, yeah. Full Winnie the Pooh.
The hell's happening?
Describe it.
I wouldn't ask him to
do that, if I were you.
It's like, um... Here we go.
It's like he was
giving birth anally,
but they quit halfway through.
They got the legs
out, and they said,
"You know what, I'm done."
Happy?
It's like he's a Muppet
from the waist down.
But this time, you can see
the Muppet's dick.
Grover's got a cock
the size of a twig.
Mr. Weasel, I can no
longer be double-parked.
I've had three tickets already.
No, no, no, DP, not again!
This has happened before?
Jesus! Either vomit or don't.
The indecision is killing me.
Why couldn't God
take my hearing?
Oh. Wow!
Cool your pits.
They're growing back.
I'm talking about your face.
I've never seen you
without your mask before.
Jesus Christ! Looks
like an avocado.
Your legs, though, they're cute.
You wanna borrow
a pair of pants?
I'm glad everybody dropped by.
You must be wondering why
I didn't call you here.
I'll tell you why I'm here.
"The Time Traveler's
Wife's" husband...
beat me within an
inch of my life.
He was torturing me!
But all I told him was
everything he wanted to know.
So, I'm here to help us gear up.
So we can go after
him without me.
No!
I'm doing this alone.
The Juggernaut
will kill you all. Fair enough.
I just need a couple of
hours to get some legs
under me. What will you do?
I don't care what
the kid did to me.
I ain't letting
Cable get to him,
even if I have to
teabag him to death.
It's really just a sip
of tea at this point.
Zip it, black Black Widow!
I'm flowing.
The first order of business is
to get me in front of Cable...
so I can pull all the fucking
blood out of his body...
and fashion his bones
into holiday jewelry.
Then, I'm gonna take his skin...
and stretch it out over
a homemade mating drum.
He's standing right
behind you, isn't he?
What in the ass?
Is this apartment listed on Tinder?
Grindr?
You picked the wrong shithole
to fuck, future boy.
Ugh. Is that really necessary?
No. It's his "Basic Instinct."
What can we help you with?
I'm here to proposition you.
Oh, boy!
He's really teeing
it up, isn't he?
Who gets to make the first joke?
I think we should all
do it at the same time.
Good call.
For $45, you get sucky-suck.
I only do over the
pants, mouth stuff.
Fuck!
The Proposition has a wonderful
Guy Pearce performance.
Wait, wait, wait! I
wanna do mine over.
Give us the line again.
I need your help!
Trust me, I'm even less happy
about this than you are...
but you unleashed the
Juggernaut, you dumb cunt!
I can't bring him down alone.
So here we are.
We're no longer
accepting applications
for X-Force, unfortunately.
Even if we were...
there's a wind advisory in
effect until at least...
We don't have a lot of time.
Your friend's about to
make his first kill.
No offense, but if
you know so much...
why not travel back to when
he was a baby, kill him then?
Or better yet, head
back a little further,
kill baby Hitler.
I use a device to
slide through time.
The longer I travel, the
harder it is to control.
I got two charges:
one to get me here,
one to get me home.
Well.
That's just lazy writing.
Your boy's gonna
kill the headmaster
of the orphanage tonight.
After that, he gets a
real taste for it.
Like 10-year-old Kirsten
Dunst, motherfucker!
So he keeps killing...
and killing, and killing,
and killing.